youclubvideo.com 2013-06-11

# Privacy - AllTimeClubbing

Privacy Statement for www.alltimeclubbing.com incl. Sub-pages 

An Operator refers to the person, company or corporation represented by a person, company or corporation that is designated on the contact page of this Website. 

The term Users refers to people who have or have not registered at the website and who, meanwhile, use the contents of the website, communicate with other users on the website or publish contents through the website. The direct use of the personal pronoun "You" is used to address you as a user of this website. 

The term Website refers to all the documents, contents, and information offered at the same internet address, under which the operations of the aforementioned materials and these Terms and Conditions are made available. The term Website also includes all its sub-directories and sub-pages. 

This document is the Privacy Statement for using the Operator's Website. The Operator dedicated himself to respect and to protect your privacy and to use any personal information gather on this Website only in accordance with the current Data Protection Laws and Regulations. 

**What is considered personal data?**

As personal data the Operator refers to the information related to your identity, such as your name, email or postal address.   
  
**Disclosure to Third Party(s)**

All data transmitted to the operator are expressly treated as confidential! In principle the Operator will not make such data available to any other parties unless you have approved such action or the Operator is obligated to disclose such data to comply with a legal obligation as for instance a court order.   
  
**For what purposes does the operator use these data?**

The Operator gathers, stores, and processes information in order to better understand the Users of this Website and to be able to improve the services offered to them. In addition, the Operator will compile internal investigations concerning the demography, user interests and user behavior. This is done anonymously; meaning no data will be used that would make it possible to identify an individual User. With your prior approval, the Operator will inform you of newly developed Website-features and other important topics about this Website on a regular basis. At any time, you have the right to cancel this permission using a written (email ? please see the contact page) statement. In addition to that, in every email-newsletter, the Operator will provide you with information on how to opt-out from receiving further information. The Operator may also store your IP-address over a period of not more than four weeks upon utilization of any services enabling you to communicate with him, with a third party, or with other Users (such as upload of media, publication of comments, etc.). This is done in order to be able to identify the individual User(s) in case of their intervention with the Operator?s Website or in case of other rights being violated. The stored information is deleted immediately after being kept for four weeks. 

**Use of Cookies**

In order to offer the Website services as user-friends as possible, this Website, as well as many well-known websites, also uses so-called Cookies. Cookies are small text files that enable recognition of a User; this way, non-first-time Users do not have to manually log-in to the Website each time they open it. Moreover, cookies can also be used to adjust the offered services according to your personal interests. The Operator uses cookies in order to analyze how the Website and its services are being used and to give out information of possible interest to you. It is however possible, to use the Website even without cookies. WWW-browsers can be adjusted to generally reject cookies. 

**Security of Data**

Although the operator strives to protect the security of your personal data in accordance with the current Data Protection Laws, yet no electronic form of communication is absolutely secure. The Operator would like to remind you that in spite of his high demands regarding data protection and privacy, all information you release voluntarily over the Internet may potentially be used by others as well. Therefore, the operator shall assume no responsibility for or liability for the disclosure of information due to data-transmission errors and/or unauthorized access through any third party. 

**Modification of this Privacy Statement**

The operator reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time and without prior notice in accordance with the current Data Protection Laws and Regulations.
